{
    "questions": [
        {
            "qid": 1,
            "question": "Are stateless widgets mutable or immutable?",
            "options": [
                "Mutable",
                "Immutable"
            ],
            "correct_answer": 2
        },
        {
            "qid": 2,
            "question": "Which widget is utilized to wrap the Column, Container, Row, or other widgets. This widget inserts the filling size around the child widget?",
            "options": [
                "Image",
                "SnackBar",
                "Padding",
                "AlertDialog"
            ],
            "correct_answer": 3
        },
        {
            "qid": 3,
            "question": "Which of the following tests a single widget?",
            "options": [
                "Unit Tests",
                "Widget Tests",
                "Interactive Tests",
                "Integration Tests"
            ],
            "correct_answer": 2
        },
        {
            "qid": 4,
            "question": "In Flutter, which of the following is used as identifiers for widgets, elements, and semantic nodes?",
            "options": [
                "Buttons",
                "Keys",
                "Widgets",
                "Streams"
            ],
            "correct_answer": 2
        },
        {
            "qid": 5,
            "question": "What are the subclasses of Key?",
            "options": [
                "GlobalKey",
                "LocalKey",
                "GlobalKey and LocalKey",
                "None of the above"
            ],
            "correct_answer": 3
        },
        {
            "qid": 6,
            "question": "The __ animation allows you to represent real-world behavior in Flutter.",
            "options": [
                "Maths-based",
                "Physics-based",
                "Graph-based",
                "None of the above"
            ],
            "correct_answer": 2
        },
        {
            "qid": 7,
            "question": "What is the refresh rate of our animation in Flutter?",
            "options": [
                "Show",
                "Refresh",
                "Ticker",
                "None of the above"
            ],
            "correct_answer": 3
        },
        {
            "qid": 8,
            "question": " Which of the following is a sequence of asynchronous events?",
            "options": [
                "Stream",
                "Flow",
                "Current",
                "None of the above"
            ],
            "correct_answer": 1
        },
        {
            "qid": 9,
            "question": "Access and manipulate the cloud database is possible with which of the following options?",
            "options": [
                "Firebase Database",
                "SQFlite Database",
                "Both A and B",
                "None of the above"
            ],
            "correct_answer": 1
        },
        {
            "qid": 10,
            "question": "Which of the given below commands checks our environment and shows the report of the status of our Flutter and Android studio apart from the IDE software installation?",
            "options": [
                "flutter clean",
                "flutter screen",
                "flutter master",
                "flutter doctor"
            ],
            "correct_answer": 4
        }
    ]
}